mashada.com 2012-11-06

# Privacy Policy - Mashada.com

## Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting Mashada.com site. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this Mashada.com site. 

The Information We Collect 

At some Mashada.com sites, you can enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, or subscribe to one of our services. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

At certain parts of some of our sites, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to order products, programs, and services or otherwise participate in the site's activities and offerings.

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g. Internet Explorer, Firefox or Safari), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Africa Online, Earthlink).

**How We Use the Information**

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us.

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your gifts or cards. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them.

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services.

If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a "letter to our editors"), we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us.

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.

We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request.

Agents and contractors of Mashada.com who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Mashada.com.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice. Inadvertent disclosures may result, for example, when third parties misrepresent their identities in asking the site for access to personally identifiable information about themselves for purposes of correcting possible factual errors in the data.

If a Mashada.com site discloses personally identifiable information to companies not owned by Mashada.com who want to market products or services to you, it will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or block such uses. For instructions on how to opt out from such disclosures, please [privacy@mashada.com](mailto:privacy@mashada.com) or go to: <http://www.mashada.com/contact.php>.

Mashada.com may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive marketing information from this site, [privacy@mashada.com](mailto:privacy@mashada.com) or go to: http://www.mashada.com/contact.

Finally, Mashada.com sites will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.

**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites, Advertisers and Sponsors**

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

Mashada.com sites sometimes may offer contests, sweepstakes, or promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with identified third parties. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes, or promotion. Mashada.com has no control over the third-party sponsors' use of this information. The Mashada.com site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if third-party sponsors will obtain such information.

Mashada.com sites may use reputable third parties to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at its web pages and to conduct research about the advertisements. Our privacy policy does not cover any use of information that such third parties may have collected from you or the methods used by the third-parties to collect that information (e.g., cookies, web beacons and clear gifs). For more information on this site's use of such third-parties, please [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy.html).

**Cookies**

To enhance your experience with our sites, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.

We may also use small pieces of code called "web beacons" or "clear gifs" to collect anonymous and aggregate advertising metrics, such as counting page views, promotion views, or advertising responses. These "web beacons" may be used to deliver cookies that conform to our cookie policy.

**Our Commitment to Security**

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

**How You can Access or Correct Information**

For instructions on how you can access the personally identifiable information that this Mashada.com site has collected about you online, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please go to: http://www.mashada.com/contact.

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about the Mashada.com online policy for this site or its implementation you may contact us at [privacy@mashada.com](mailto:privacy@mashada.com), or by going to: http://www.mashada.com/contact.
